{
    "subject": "resource/The_Formula_(1980_film)",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/linguistics/gold/hypernym",
    "object": "resource/Film",
    "human_readable": "The Formula (1980 film) is a type of Film.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7600148320198059,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6645529270172119,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6306437849998474,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.562502920627594,
            "question": "What year was the film 'The Formula' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5616058707237244,
            "question": "Which actors starred in the film 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4782816171646118,
            "question": "What are some themes explored in the film 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4751878082752228,
            "question": "Can you name other films from the same genre as 'The Formula'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4659143090248108,
            "question": "Was the film 'The Formula' a critical or commercial success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35519808530807495,
            "question": "Is 'The Formula' a documentary or a fictional story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3100231885910034,
            "question": "Where could I watch or stream the film 'The Formula'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Formula (1980 film) is a type of Film.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7966_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is 'The Formula' a documentary or a fictional story?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7966_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Was the film 'The Formula' a critical or commercial success?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7966_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name other films from the same genre as 'The Formula'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7966_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7966_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents describe \"The Formula\" as a 1980 film directed by John G. Avildsen and starring Marlon Brando, George C. Scott, and Marthe Keller. This clearly indicates that it is of the type \"Film.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}